you know the story we hear the next day
mom throws Boyd in the gorilla enclosure
2016 also brought us stuff like you
remember gorilla Gate the boy that fell
into the gorilla enclosure see that's
how crazy 2016 was I said gorilla gate
company like yeah then I went the boy oh
yeah that gorilla and so that that's
right that there were so many gorilla
incidents we got lost track of them boy
falls into the to the gorilla enclosure
they should kill the gorilla to save the
boy that was a horrible story it was a
sad story cuz that was a beautiful
animal you saw the it was beautiful I'm
gonna be honest because I'm honest with
every audience I perform in front of
imma be honest when I heard the story
board mom at the zoo loses track of the
boy boy gets in the gorilla enclosure
they shouldn't kill the animal to save
the boy I didn't see a picture and I
didn't see a video my first thought
honestly my first thought was all white
people
that was my first thoughts oh ye of
course white people can't keep track of
the kids of course that's what happened
then I saw the picture and the video do
you know is a black family I thought oh
my goodness this changes everything
first of all that woman's gonna lose her
black bomber card that's what's gonna
happen she's gonna lose her black mama
card now this is what we know okay this
is well we know eye witnesses people
standing nearby so the boys for moms at
the zoo she's got other kids and the boy
says I'm going in that gorilla enclosure
and the mom says no you're not and the
boy says yes I am and then that point is
when I lost my mind cuz that's a black
man who has a black mama I didn't know
that you can say something back to mama
after mama said something to you that
isn't she cold I didn't have as a kid my
goodness cause let me tell you something
this is me at 4:00 with my mom let me
tell you folks something my mom was a
bad man if my mom was a bad man and if
that's me at the zoo at 4:00 with my mom
just that we don't hear the same story
we heard about this boy if we don't hear
that that story doesn't even develop the
same way I'm four at the zoo with my mom
I'm going in that gorilla enclosure no
you're not yes I am you know story we
hear the next day mom throws Boyd in the
gorilla enclosure all right there is
that so let's go let's go he lives there
now come on let's go start a big debate
it did it went to the Internet that
started a big debate people to hashtag
justice for Harambee we got to get
justice for the people want to bring the
mom up on charges they don't know the
mom they weren't there
oh we got to do look I'm gonna tell you
something bout the Internet the Internet
is the greatest and the worst invention
we've ever done it's great sure it is
great because it makes the world smaller
brings us closer together
it is horrible because it lets everyone
believe that their opinion is important
and it's not theirs not at all there's
not at all
it's a lot of people just people who's
fought this and whose fault is it is it
the mom's fault is it the zoo's fault
I still Paul shall we buy applause how
many people think it was the zoo's fault
bye applause okay all right couple part
my applause how many people think it was
the mom's fault okay
all right by the way that's not
everybody that's interesting because the
people that didn't vote those are the
only two choices I'm not really sure
what's going on here that was high these
people I go when he says gorillas imma
jump in I'm gonna jump in on gorillas
when he's on gorillas I'm a joke oh I
missed it there's no gorillas I missed
the boat I missed the boat and that's
how Trump got elected
I missed the vote I missed the vote I
only tell that joke here to see the
applause but I like the other people
like if you want no one whose fault it
is it's neither one of those two will go
back this is society's fault this takes
a good long harsh look in the mirror
because once again somebody convinced us
that the way that we were raising our
kids was wrong the way you were raised
was wrong the way I was raised was wrong
and we can't discipline kids like that
anymore
not in public cuz that kid will end up
with low self-esteem
you know how this fight happened to the
kid he might not end up in the middle of
a gorilla enclosure that's what happened
to the kid
I'm going in that gorilla enclosure no
you're not yes I am Wow you can go to
all the therapy you want to but guess
what we just saved the gorilla look I'm
different different than a lot of comics
you may have seen just in your lifetime
I'm different i watch the specials that
are being filmed for a vigil and do my
little research I see all the comics
that come out they poke a little fun at
you guys they do I see if you've been to
more than one show you come out you see
them they're like oh there's always that
tongue-in-cheek
look at me I finally made it filming my
special in Utah you know that time but
they're like oh it's great to be in
Provo wink wink
look I'm a little different i'ma say
this with all sincerity and honesty
ladies and gentlemen it is a pleasure to
be back in Provo Utah
here's the deal
I've done this a very long time my only
perform in eight places in the United
States per year eight places that's it
very selective about those places it's
only eight places the majority of my
income is made by working in Canada a
lot of times after the show people ask
me what are those eight places and I
tell them it's it's a long list of it
but it rotates about eight every year in
Seattle
it's Oregon my hometown San Diego my
home club is the comedy and magic club
in Hermosa Beach California
it's Detroit Milwaukee Boston and also
on that list is Utah and they got all
those yes well we're in Utah and I only
tell them Salt Lake City I tell them
Salt Lake City because let's be truthful
outside of this state that's the only
city the average American knows it's in
Utah I don't give them the list I don't
have time to point out on a map I don't
tell them Ogden West Valley City Park
City Provo Price you heard me price
price I've been multiple times to price
so you people don't scare me you
understand what I'm saying
none you have here that scares me eight
places that's it eight places United
States a lot of times people ask me why
that is and I tell them the truth
I've done this a long time I've done
this since I was 17 years old
there's no this November that'll be 35
years that this has been my job that's
nice of you the rest you people I'll
give you a chance to do math via because
yes this is this is 51 this right here
is 51 because black don't cry that's 51
a lot of times people ask me why what is
it why is it the only work in the eight
places and I tell them the truth
30 plus years of doing this I have run
out of patience for the stupidity of the
average American audience
so I'm narrowed it down to eight places
where when I show up I know that you
guys will understand what the hell I'm
talking about
we we are working on some sort of IQ
reduction program in this country that I
can't fight the battle anymore we are
getting stupider as a society and I know
stupider not even a real word but if I
said more stupidness towards going it
means stupider be right back to where we
started out if we wonder why no you're
sitting there you're wondering what's
the act dying what is the Act about what
I'll tell you it's clean as the
prerequisite but there's also an edge oh
there's an edge I'm not young I told you
I'm 51 I'm not the happy peppy chipper
comic comes out here with all the energy
go I hope they like me I don't care I
don't I don't I don't I don't care I
come out and just do what it is I do now
I try to view the audience to see what
goes on because I try to help out people
I know there's a lot of young people
here I know it's not legal when I do
this but I do when I perform I do a lot
of outside the eight clubs I do a lot of
theaters and I try to skew that audience
to be 35 and up because that is my
audience I'll be honest with you if
you're below 35 don't even talk to me
don't I I got nothing to hear from you
you don't know anything about life keep
it to yourself I don't I don't want to
hear anything out of your mouth to you
35 years old
[Applause]
you're not an adult to get 35 as far as
I'm concerned you can sit with the rest
of the kids at the card table and
Thanksgiving tell you 35 and then move
on over to the big table that's what I
say and look guys look at the future I
know the people our Father they're with
me look at the young people here they're
little angry he's talking about I'm 24
I'm gonna dump really camera in a car
shut up that's what I'm done so I'm done
we're the Millennials the young folks
where are you where that's energy that's
what I like to hear how old are you my
dear
24 I was very pronounced uh she said I
am 24 I'm part of that joke here's what
I say I do try to help now as much as I
am this guy it talks about out of the
money and stuff like that I do try to
help I will defend your generation
because here's the knock on the
Millennials in their generation you hear
it all the time but young people you
hear that when you work that you're
coddled generation and then when you get
turned out into the real world you're
not ready for the real world and you end
up back at home right that's the knock
on them that's not their fault don't
ever talk about them they're saying
that's their fault that's not on them
that's on you as a parent because at
some point in time we change parenting
and somebody told the young people who
you have to tell them to follow their
dreams just encourage them you don't
listen to anyone you just follow your
dreams no matter what somebody says they
get turned out in the real world and
they realize there's no financial
backing for a cat water park and then
they're back in your house that's you
that's your phone
I tried to bring them in the show early
cuz i know cuz right now 24 i'm gonna
talk up here for 40 45 minutes and then
you're gonna sit there and stare and
wonder why people are laughing at me but
in 10 years you'll think I'm a genius
that's how it works so I try to help at
24 you enjoy every bit of your life at
24 I give you the facts of life and all
the people that are out there that are
in that same age range enjoy every bit
of it the real facts of life
not the stuff that's peddled to you the
real raw honest facts of life that life
is unfair life is ironic life does not
always work out am I right so far life
is hilarious at times when it shouldn't
be
not everyone gets a trophy there's no
such thing as a participant ribbon in
his first second or third place if you
don't get one of those and you just tell
people you were there you understand
that nobody came back from Brazil with a
participant ribbon that's what I'm
saying enjoy every bit of your life
because in 24 the truth of life is at 24
we had about four more years tell it's
different
I'm not saying over I'm just saying this
difference you taking things for granted
24 24 I bet you can eat a meal and then
do something right afterwards can't I
bet you can
yeah you hold on to that the body can't
be multitasking like that forever 51
years old even sandwich me in the middle
of a conversation she go oh I got a lie
down I got a lie down
yeah I just ain't like into that just to
talk to you but I can't do both I will
talk to you after my nap but right now I
need to be in a bed that's where I need
to be and people hear me talk about this
and they get angry they go don't tell
young people that life begins at 40 mm
life is well over by 40 it's your hectic
Kathryn by 28 look if you want to know
what the perfect model for life is
Benjamin Button that's the perfect model
for life because you're Pete physically
and mentally at the same time 24 that's
the top of the game you're an athlete
you're strong you could run you could
jump but if somebody said use that
effectively in a competition you
wouldn't know how to do it and by the
time you got the wisdom maybe do it
effectively you can't get out of a chair
try to bring people on board people in
denial there I try to bring them on
board how old are you sir
forty-six how old are you my friend
51 gentleman here arm cross 50 all right
we're all about to say but that's
doesn't matter where we were if we were
even 30-something they we're still the
same cuz we're past 28
because that's what it is is it because
you know what so what we say on a
regular basis the 24 never says I think
I slept wrong last night play the young
faces in this room they don't even know
what I'm talking about just don't you
just fall asleep oh yeah you used to
then went to one night you're getting
ready for bed waiting for that to happen
I gotta get ready for beds cuz last
Wednesday I slept wrong and then I was
messed up till Friday so this time wait
till you wake up in the morning with
gray hair and acne what in the world how
am I going backwards and forwards at the
same time I wish I had better news for
you young people I do I wish you so you
got four years you enjoy it coasting all
the way and then 28 just ride it on out
cuz there are times I Drive by the
cemetery oh you lucky scoundrels look at
you I wish you got better I wish it did
don't doesn't at all that's what I've
become in this that's what I've been
coming to my all day I'm at a port in my
life if you click technology got a lot
of Technology going on if anybody asks
you cuz they might they say hey when did
Lamont quit on technology you tell them
51 that's when I quit I've clocked out
51 I got enough got enough up here don't
need any more got it all I'm good but I
know everything I don't pay attention to
it anymore I'm good I'm fine
I know that you don't want to drew the
line snapchat that's when I drew the
line I did I know I I don't know what it
is I don't know I know the young people
you know what it is cuz you use it I
don't know and don't tell me I don't
want it up here I don't want it I don't
want it it sounds dirty in the first
place it does sounds dirty
you want to see my snapchat No
how would you say that this is mixed
company no it's a photo app I know that
much it's a photo app because this is
what this society is we love taking
pictures because there's no
accountability you have to make any
decisions okay until here's 1,500
pictures of me I just went outside for
10 minutes look at that there's it cuz
you just take pictures tell the battery
and the camera dies that's it
see it's a different generation folks my
age we had to make decisions because our
camera had 24 pictures and you had to
make harsh decisions about what you took
picture their ties your friends go hey
could you take a picture of me like whoo
I got three laughs oh no no yeah I got
you on another roll so now I'm I can't
do that try I'm at a point in my life
where I just want respect I don't care
whether it's earned or not when I go to
the bank I like to be called mr.
Ferguson mr. Ferguson that's what I like
to be called you know what I found out
that title directly associated with the
balance at your bank account that's what
that is you got to have at least a comma
at least a comma won't get you mister do
you walk in the bank with 46 bucks in
your bank account that's a first name
bank account that's what that is
46 bucks what's up dude that's a 46
bucks is are you gotta watch out cuz it
happens fast you didn't realize how fast
it happens oh well the time it wasn't
the bank it felt good I had a thousand
ten dollars in my bank account they go
what can we do for a day mr. Ferguson
I'd like to withdraw $20 here's your
money Lamont it happens FS as a comic
the first place you get to choose your
level of respect when you travel is on
the point when you buy the plane ticket
you get to put have that pull down menu
that's the first place you go to they
get to choose mr. mrs. MS dr. ooh look
talking about respect maybe I should
take doctor I'm here to tell you do not
take doctor because that one can
backfire on you because you could be on
the plane and they actually need a
doctor and then you are over one in your
medical career so do not take dr. Yeoh I
am on every single flight people don't
even realize this an option I am
professor on every single flights
professor that will never backfire
because never in the history of aviation
has there ever been an educational
emergency never
is there a professor on board no that's
never been asked anyone if it was how
bad could it be as their professor why
yes I'm a professor what seems to be the
problem this plane left Chicago at 8:00
a.m. going 500 miles an hour no one's
ever asked that so where I sit it's all
try to do try to just make things a
little better I'm looking at the year
we're in the 2017 this all right to be
honest with you the measure is just as
long as it's not 2016 right because 2016
was a horribly 2016 was horrible and
surprising it brought us stuff that we
never thought about and that was a
situation 2016 brought us clowns
yeah you heard me clowns clowns there
was a clown's situation in 2016 you
gonna do about all these clowns clowns
was a thing cleanse I don't even know
how we still have clowns like like how
are they a thing like how are we still
nobody likes some nobody likes them at
all they're scary they're creepy
nobody likes so the breakdown pit
everybody thinks is scary and creepy and
the only thing that they keep clowns
alive are clowns does the only thing
that's going on the clown lobby is very
strong it goes guns alcohol clowns
that's the lobby ranking people don't
even realize that they're scary no one
no one no one likes them no one then
I'll tell you how powerful they are take
a look around all the people are in this
room right now we could put up a pretty
good stand if we had some type of enemy
invasion
if one clown walked in here right now
we'd be like oh we gotta go we gotta go
no there's one clown that can't be good
why is one clown here no what no one
clown no that's not good 50 clowns sure
that's funny they came in one car but
not one clown no my mom was a bad like I
said my mom's a bad man I don't mean was
as in past tense still I've talked to
her today still like I'm talking about
in her mama Prime she was a bad man I'm
the oldest of four children my mother's
a stay-at-home mom my father was a
nuclear engineer gone all the time
uh so when you get in the house here in
the house with four kids mmm
makes you a little crazy my mom once
said to us your father's going to come
home and find you kids buried in the
backyard
yeah you hear that windy 7:00 it's time
to straighten up and listen to the crazy
woman because you know it's 7:00 I'm
only going on here say that I'm the
oldest think about that that's what she
said to us those were I can quit and get
a phone right now and call my mom she
will verify this that's what she said to
us your father's gonna come home find
you kids buried in the backyard that's
what she said
you understand the impact of that that
means in her head she had already killed
us do you understand that it was a done
deal
she had killed us and buried us birth in
our own backyard didn't even try to hide
us like here they are here they are
right here
I didn't take me to jail so I can get
some peace and quiet my mom's favorite
phrase you had all day it's my mom's
favorite phrase anyone elses your head
all day what she meant by that was no
matter what you were about to do you had
all day to do it
now you just messing up her day we're
about to go to the store okay I got to
go to the bathroom you had all day to go
to the bathroom and you wait and tell
now here's the beauty of that that's
crazy logic but there's the beauty of
that it helps I use it today not with my
kids just in general I'm driving down
the street somebody turns left in front
of me you had all day to turn left and
you wait until now little fired up I
have the kids that'll do it I have kids
my four kids which is too many kids that
is for kids is way too many kids look if
this was 18 17 sure have four kids 20 17
no reason for me to have four kids there
are no more fields to plow no reason
you have four kids my kids are spread
all throughout the historical timeline
I'll give you the oldest I'll give you
the youngest and the people that are
staring at me you'll understand all this
crankiness on September 3rd of this year
my oldest Alex will turn 29 years old on
September 27th of the same year Olivia
youngest's will turn four oh yes it's
like that yes because I found out that
apparently my lot in life is to produce
a new human being every decade like an
automaker just roll it out on the
assembly line would you take a look at
that that is the 2010 Ferguson won't you
take a look at that yes indeed it's a
hybrid and now we're filming I'd still
would like to acknowledge the crowd
we'll see what's going on and then I
cannot oversee this I just had to get
stuff out of the way first to establish
that we're doing something I'm guessing
congratulations is in order
you're quite welcome when is the date or
I weigh this is a butto we're married
we're married or what what's this what
are we getting me okay that's what I
thought April 4th all right uh how long
has the courtship been year and a half
how old are you 21 hold up I waited for
a beat I did I waited for a beat because
even in Utah there were some judgment
that took place right there that was
that time that was judgment from Utah
that went
[Music]
courtship year-and-a-half 21 all right I
wish you the best let me ask you this
how did what's your name sir
man good-looking couple by the way quite
well how did how did he propose he took
you back to where you had your first
kiss and the Year marker okay very nice
then again cuz he took me back to where
we had our first kiss that was a year
and a half ago for crying out loud
that's not that much of the memory thing
that took place is what it is
he also lit fireworks all right man all
right
oh he lit fight wait he lit fireworks
after your first kiss oh there were
fireworks okay I thought whole this is
this this is gettin Vince's serial
killer type of rarity on our first kiss
there were fireworks I always knew you
were the one hold out Matt wait a minute
wait a second man here's where I'm gonna
go
first of all well this is a different
it's an anomaly you guys know Utah's an
anomaly as far as how this goes 21 and
then if this was we were outside of Utah
and they go 21 we're getting married
people were like oh we got to stop this
but you guys are like hmm okay welcome
to the village let me get a little
public service announcement I'm not sure
if this will help you now but later on
in life this might help you I tried the
dis to do this this is for women a
public service announcement on behalf of
all men if there are married people here
married women you sit atop on everyone
else you listen more intently than
anyone else in this room what I'm about
to tell you ladies bugs every single man
in this room but we've never told you
about it that's why I call it a public
service announcement let's try to help
out as far as what it goes married women
more intently anyone else here well
women living with a guy underneath them
woman don't fit into those two
categories underneath them that
encompasses every single woman here but
listen in that order of importance
ladies to you on behalf of all men
through me ladies if you come home and
your man says to you hey Jane called she
said she wants you to call her back that
was the message all right there was no
line of questioning that needs to follow
this the message relay is complete well
what did she say she said she wants you
to call her back well how did she say it
did she sound hungry are you kidding
ladies I don't know what happens when
you leave the house I don't know what
type of special operative Jack Bauer
Jason Bourne's secret agent life you
were living but I swear to you on behalf
of all men here we are not withholding
any codes from you just call the woman
back just call her back
why can't just call her back blind
they're gonna find out what it is she
wanted I wonder what time she called
then take a look at the women looking to
meet with blank stares he's silly he
don't know let me show you why it's a
little crazy man comes home pay a steep
called said he want you to call them
back
all right thanks that's it the end
there's no what how much Steve sound is
he trapped in a well do I need to get a
posse now and here while I'm at it
ladies keep listening there's no order
this is all women same level what say
it's been a long day you and your man
have been out it's been a long day
you're running errands doing a bunch of
stuff you get a chance get anything to
eat on your way home you decide let's
stop at the fast-food place get some
food and take it back to the house and
while ordering your man turns to you and
says would you like some french fries
and you say no that was your chance
there is no reason that once we pulled
to the window they hand us the bag now
we can't drive with a bag so we hand you
the bag now it's a race to get home cuz
you're sitting there talking and eating
and talking to me and those are our
fries that is the sound of men who have
lost many a french fry in the
battlefield of life we love you to death
ladies but oh my goodness you get in
there you start eating and just talking
and and in the middle you have this
realization go you know what those
aren't even my fries you're right
they're not your fries yeah had your
chance said this one night a woman
looked me dead in the face and said they
taste better when there is and every
man's head in the room exploded and
every woman did exactly what you did
yeah that's right finally someone put
that in the words that's exactly right
now also let me gonna tell you this now
this is not public service announcement
still has to do with men and women I
gotta be very delicate about what I'm
about to talk about I'm not gonna
generalize it's not all women okay I'm
not gonna say it's all women here's the
scenario when you're out at a restaurant
ladies you got it you're out at a
restaurant
okay then guys we just questions ladies
like I said very gingerly as I walk you
what how come when you're out at a
restaurant ladies you can't just order
what it says on the menu why can't you
just look at the menu and order the
words it says on the menu every time
that menu shows up women it's a
suggestion that's all that goes on there
oh this is very nice I see where you're
going with this but here's what I'd like
to do I like to take a couple lines from
this dish and a couple hiders from that
dish I'm making a whole new dish and
then I saw it there's a restaurant up
the street that has some things you
don't have you could just send somebody
down there and
there's an herb I like if you plant it
I'll wait just order what it says men
don't do this by the way we don't I've
done the research we don't do this you
know what if we do anything if we do
anything you don't we do we take away
that's all we do
hey this has bell pepper on it not a big
fan of bell pepper not too much trouble
could you not put bell pepper on it okay
that's it women every time that menu
shows up it's an episode of chopped
every single time people fly into the
kitchen I found out not your fault it's
not your fault ladies it's not it's not
it's what it's called that's the problem
it's a menu menu menu menu order from
here room we have no idea where you're
ordering from what we need is a will
menu we need a little menu it's just a
big piece of paper it's got a picture
the earth on it now this is a restaurant
I like this this is what we're looking
for this is why I think differently it's
eight places you know any places that
people go okay we get it we see what
goes up outside of those eight places oh
my goodness especially with young people
I got it like I said I tried to bring
young people in in the eight places I
can try and do my best to bring the
young people in outside the egg places
who I have a better chance of making
young people outside of those eight
places laughs with my car keys then I
would attend justice I should I just
walk I do
if I can make fart noises on their
bellies I'd be a genius is what I'm
saying
I just think differently that's all
watching TV it doesn't help I watch I
was watching the Miss USA pageant
recently and I've come to conclusion
that the most useless part of any beauty
pageant is the question-and-answer
portion of the beauty pageant like it
has always you watch at home and you can
awkward your cringe like old can we
notch as we just skip through them cuz
it is it's very awkward they ask these
questions of these ladies and there's no
reason to ask them that's never gonna
come up in the job at all you know it's
it's complicated questions miss Rhode
Island how do you think we'd be able to
take care of world hunger miss miss
Pennsylvania how do you think we'd be
able to achieve peace in the Middle East
look there's no reason to ask these
ladies these questions matter of fact
they should just title that segment
worst-case scenario because do you know
how many things would have to go
horribly wrong before Miss USA got
handcuffed to the nuclear football do
you know how many people would have to
die before miss Arkansas got to
implement her policies the layers
president vice-president Speaker of the
House the Regional Sales Manager at
Quiznos
she's not even first in line in the
beauty patches like Miss America is
ahead of Miss USA and as far as I think
Captain America may be ahead of it I'm
not sure I always get that confused what
do you think first is Captain America or
Miss America which one do you think
captain they'll get missing yet Miss
America's right because Captain America
isn't real so fascinated by pegs are
fascinated by sports I like sports I
like sports events where both
competitors are prepared for the contest
to begin look we're in an outdoorsy you
guys camping fishing only one of the
athletes is aware that the game is afoot
Southern California there's a fishing
show on the radio every weekend fishing
fishing on the radio I didn't know
fishing was so complicated they had to
have a guy help them out with when you
think about what fishing is seriously I
know there are people here that fish I
don't care the essence of fishing is you
trying to outsmart a fish and the fish
are winning because they're still fish
you understand that there are no more
dodo birds cuz we won we're man we're
top of the food chain yet we still can't
beat these fish we got radar depth
finders yet you can boats oh we go out
the pit yeah you can go fishing come on
with no fish fish have no technology you
understand the point I'm making here
none there are no fish meetings all
right everybody gather round gather
around we're still battling the Evolve
errs hey what have you got well been
thinking about it looks like our best
bet is still swim away all right we're
gonna go with
it said it's how I think it's how I see
things like I said I saw crazy things we
all saw crazy things in 2016 this is the
craziest thing I saw cuz I see things
differently
now I remember I work in Canada all the
time this summer when I was up in Canada
this is the craziest thing that I saw
everything in Calgary there was a high
speed police chase in Calgary that
lasted seven hours a seven-hour
high-speed police chase in Calgary
that's crazy to be first of all seven
hours police check that means either you
have nothing to do or they're the most
patient police on the face of the earth
is what it is seven hour here's the
other thing about it they never left the
city never left that's not even a chase
that's just a complex game of
hide-and-go-seek that's all that is
seven hours never leave the city here's
the story man and a woman stole a
vehicle let the police on the seven-hour
police chase like I said that's Canada
man that's they got patients up there
nobody's chasing anybody in the States
for seven hours cops get a little itchy
and depending on what you look like oh
my goodness you chased somebody for
seven hours you better at least want a
Heisman Trophy I'm gonna tell you that
that's the only way they gonna change me
for seven hours the people that are
clapping I like that the people that are
stunned
oh well that's on you I brought this to
the village man and woman steal a truck
seven hours police chase I think that is
the greatest commercial I've ever seen
for that vehicle that's what that should
be seven hours they never left the city
those are City miles not highway miles
city miles never left the city that
should be the commercial just show the
chase and then and then at the end boom
for an escape almost that should be
that should be the commercial seven
hours never let the police go oh they
were arrested without incident without
isn't it did you not hear seven hours as
that was going on that's a work shift
seven hours it's quite conceivable that
a policeman was halfway through his
shift then had to clock out the next
night come on what do we do you chase
him that's what you do you go tag you're
it that's what you do they took pride in
it and I'm like really
it took pride like oh we arrested the
man and woman without any in seven hours
that was a man and a woman did we hear
the first part a man and a woman in a
car for seven hours that was a mutual
surrender is what that was like though I
gotta get away from her and she don't
get away from me take me to jail so I
can have some quiet is what I need seven
hours now look I said you're outdoors
for people you know you go on long
drives you can't you do this stuff think
about the last time you were in the car
for seven hours with your spouse think
about seven hours and no police were
chasing you you know that car's just saw
seven hours she's sitting over there
looking at the I think I think they're
getting closer
oh I know they're chasing us of course
the in closer I'm trying to concentrate
just try to help me that's all I'm
trying to do just help okay okay I'm
sorry okay yeah just okay seven hours
it's a lot of time some point this
happened okay what what what does that
know that means something what does that
mean what it's just kind of hungry oh
you're hungry you're hot we're being
chased by the police well how are you
hungry yeah ain't all the fries I had to
two fries is what I have how is it
possible that you're hungry
sorry just seven hours long time seven
hours a woman in a car what what is it
what I gotta pee you gotta be you gotta
pee right now we're being chased by the
police you got a beat
yeah had all day to go creep into the
rifle we're not here
[Applause]
you